alldb.in 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy - Wowsome

Privacy Policies for "wowsome.com", hereinafter referred to as "we", "our" or "us" in this Privacy Statement "You" hereinafter is referred to as ("Your Parents" in the case of minors who are required to take their consent) or "The Registered User" or "Any other User" who uses this site. 

We display Ads using Google Adsense. You should read Google's privacy policy at: <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>.

### General:

This Privacy Statement provides information about what personal information Topper collects and how we use that information in India, whether provided on or off-line. This Privacy Statement also provides direction on what to do if you do not want your personal information collected or shared and how to contact our company with respect to personal information. By access and use of this Website (the "Site"), you accept and agree to be bound by and comply with these legal terms of use (the "Disclaimer"). By using this Web site, you represent that you have read and understood these terms and conditions and agree to be bound by these terms and conditions. Furthermore, by using this Web site, you represent that (i) you have the capacity to be bound by these terms and conditions and (ii) if you are acting on behalf of a company or other entity, you have the authority to bind such company or entity.

### Personal Information:

We collect and use your personal information to respond to your inquiries, and to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services. We reserve the right at all times to collect, use and disclose any information where required or permitted by law or regulatory authority to do so or to protect the legitimate interests of Topper. We do not transfer your personal information to any third party for any purpose whatsoever. Being an open forum, the profile that you fill is visible to all the users. Most of your details except your phone no will be visible to the other users. So it is required that you take proper discretion in filling those details. You are required to ask your parents and not to fill any details without their permission. We reserve the right to use your contact details to contact you directly through post or telephone. However this information will never be shared with any third party.

### Children Policy:

Children Under 13 years of age are not allowed on our website. We do not keep any such accounts with us knowingly. If you know an account please inform us. We will remove them immediately. Others children are recommended to join only after consent of their parents.

### Links

Our Site may contain links to other websites. We will not be responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to this website. There is a lot of user generated content. The users are requested to inform any maligning links etc.

### Your Consent

If you provide your personal information, we assume that you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of it as described at the time of collection and as outlined in this Privacy Statement. Your consent may be express or implied, depending on the circumstances and the sensitivity of the personal information in question. If you do not consent, please do not provide your personal information or, where applicable, exercise the opt-in or opt-out options offered.

### Use Without Consent 

There are instances where we may collect, use or disclose your personal information without your consent, for example to collect a debt you owe to us, to comply with a subpoena or court order, or to comply with the rules of court regarding the production of records or to comply with the directions of any quasi judicial, regulatory or any government authority.

### Third party Advertisements:

Our Site may contain links to other websites. We will not be responsible for the privacy Advertisements sometimes automatically receive your IP address. When this happens, these advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. We does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by us and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

### "Cookies" - What information is being stored? 

From time to time we may set up websites in support of specific promotions. When you view one of our websites or on-line advertisements or promotions, we may store some information on your computer in the form of "cookies" or similar files. This information stored on your computer's hard drive does not contain any personal information, but enables us to communicate more meaningfully with you. These cookies also enable you to use our website more efficiently by storing your login information. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase cookies from your hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or Help screen to learn more about these functions. As most Websites do, however, we do track usage patterns on our Website on an anonymous basis. Your identity cannot reasonably be ascertained from this information. Each time you visit our Website, we record your Internet Service Provider, the date and time of your visit, the pages you visit and the documents downloaded, the searches you performed, and the referring URL's you came from. We use this non-personal information to optimise our Website service. Not permitting use of cookies will render this site unusable.

### Changes to this Statement

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Statement at any time and we will take reasonable steps to advise you of any material changes. However, you should review this Privacy Statement from time to time to ensure that you are aware of and accept any changes made. For example, your continued consent to our collection, use and disclosure practices following notification of any material change and/or your continued access of our Website following the posting on the Website of any material changes to the privacy statement will signify your acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, the terms of the modified Privacy Statement. At any time, if you do not consent to our privacy policy, you are requested to discontinue usage.
